sigelectronics.com 2014-11-22

# SIG Electronics, Privacy Policies

**SIG Electronics Privacy Policies**

  * Privacy Policy
  * Information collection and Use
  * Registration
  * Order
  * Sharing
  * Your Access to and Control over Information
  * Children
  * Security
  * Links
  * Surveys and Contests
  * Terms and Conditions, Notices, and Revisions

**Terms & Conditions**

**SIG Electronics Policies**

**Return Policy**

**Electronics Products Recycling Association (EPRA)**

| 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (http://www.sigelectronics.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through SIG Electronics.com, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data?
  * Are children allowed to use SIG Electronics.com?
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * What about links?
  * What information is required when I join a contest?
  * Terms and Conditions, Notices, and Revisions.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

SIG Electronics.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collected information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items.

Back to Top

**REGISTRATION  
**  
In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important SIG Electronics.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail. 

Back to Top

**ORDER**

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order or wire transfer. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.

Back to Top

**SHARING  
**  
We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes. 

| Canada Post | Purolator | USPS  
---|---|---  
4567 Dixie Rd | 5995 Avebury Road | 475 L'Enfant Plaza, SW  
Mississauga, Ontario | Mississauga, Ontario | Washington, DC  
L4W 1S2  | L5R 3T8  | 20260-2202  
1-866-607-6301 | 1-888-744-7123 | 1-800-222-1811  
  
Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website. 

Back to Top

**YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION**  

Customers may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via e-mail ([webmaster@sigelectronics.com](mailto:webmaster@sigelectronics.com)) or phone number given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/update any data we have about you.
  * Have us remove any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

Back to Top

**CHILDREN**

SIG Electronics does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use SIG Electronics.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. SIG Electronics is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.

Back to Top

**SECURITY**

SIG Electronics takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the webpage. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Back to Top

**LINKS**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SIG Electronics.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

Back to Top

**SURVEYS AND CONTESTS**

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our website. 

Back to Top

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS**

If you choose to visit SIG Electronics.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law. If you have any concern about privacy at SIG Electronics.com, please contact us ([webmaster@sigelectronics.com](mailto:webmaster@sigelectronics.com)) and we'll try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions will change also. We will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected.

If you have opted out of receiving communications from SIG Electronics.com, you still be able to view news of policy changes at www.sigelectronics.com. Otherwise, you may e-mail us at ([webmaster@sigelectronics.com](mailto:webmaster@sigelectronics.com)) to ask about changes and updates. 

Back to Top
